<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ppl</string>
    <string-array name="navigation_drawer_items_array">
        <item>Connect</item>
        <item>Fixtures</item>
        <item>Table</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="international">World</string>
    <string name="national">India</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="profile">Me</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_screen">Notification</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string-array name="gen">
        <item>Choose Gender</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Male</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="edu_details">
        <item>Choose Educational Details</item>
        <item>Government Service</item>
        <item>Student</item>
        <item>Serviceman</item>
        <item>Teacher/Professor</item>
        <item>Others</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="international1">After drying out from near-record rainfall that
        swamped Paris last month, the French capital awoke this morning to a white blanket
        of snowfall thick enough to shut down the famed Eiffel Tower.
        Around 5 inches of snow has fallen there in the past 24 hours, according to
        French official weather service Meteo France.</string>
    <string name="international2">South Korea is gearing up to host the 2018 Pyeongchang
        Winter Olympics starting with Friday’s opening ceremony for the 2,925
        athletes from 92 countries, the largest ever in winter games history. Among them
        will be 22 athletes from communist neighbor North Korea, a team officially welcomed
        to participate at the last minute by the International Olympic Committee (IOC).</string>

    <string name="national1">“Unfounded allegations are being made regarding the
        2016 Inter-Governmental Agreement (IGA) to procure 36 Rafale aircraft in fly-away
        condition from France. This would normally not have merited a response but
        for the serious damage being caused by the misleading statements, sought to be
        repeatedly perpetrated on a serious matter of national security,” the Defence Ministry said in a statement.</string>
    <string name="national2">After days of protest against what they termed the neglect of Andhra Pradesh
        in the Union Budget, the Telugu Desam Party (TDP) spoke out in the Lok Sabha accusing the BJP-led
        NDA government of injustice towards the newly formed State and only paying attention to immediate
        electoral gains rather than promises made to it.</string>
    <string name="test">China export growth accelerated in January amid mounting trade tension
        with Washington while imports surged as factories stocked up ahead of the Lunar New Year holiday.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps__locate_me">Map</string>
</resources>
